lawinsider.com 2018-12-21

# Privacy Policy

LAST UPDATED: 11/7/2018

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Privacy Policy governs data collection and usage of the products, services, software, platform and websites (collectively, "Services") provided by LawInsider and any of our affiliates (collectively, "LawInsider"). By using the Services, you consent to the data practices described in this policy as well as our Terms of Service. If you do not agree to any part of this Privacy Policy, then you should stop accessing the Services.  

## 1\. Collection of your Personal Information

LawInsider may collect personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, physical address, telephone number, or employment information. If you purchase our Services, we will collect and store your billing and credit card information. LawInsider may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your Postal Code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. LawInsider will not delete customer information for paying members. However, LawInsider reserves the right to delete customer information for members with a free account status at any time.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by LawInsider. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times, operating system, cookie information, referring website addresses, and Internet Service Provider. This information is used by LawInsider for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Services. In order to better understand how users use its site and to improve its services, LawInsider may also collect information on your use of our Site, such as pages visited, links clicked, text entered, and mouse movements.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through the Services, this information may be collected and used by others. LawInsider encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from our website so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. LawInsider is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the websites we operate

## 2\. Use of your Personal Information

LawInsider collects and uses your personal information to operate our websites and deliver the Services you have requested. LawInsider may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from LawInsider and its affiliates. LawInsider may also contact you to participate in surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

LawInsider does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. LawInsider may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party without your express consent.

In addition, LawInsider may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, perform tasks required to complete a purchase transaction, provide customer support, arrange for deliveries. LawInsider may also share information on your use of our Site, such as pages visited, links clicked, non-sensitive text entered, and mouse movements, with third party providers of web analytic software in order to enable LawInsider to improve its services. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these Services, and they are obligated to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Additionally, if you order our Services through a third party, or if you order our Services through a co-branded web page, LawInsider may share personal information and information about your use of our Services with the third party to enable them to contact you regarding their products and/or services. In such cases, the third party's use of information furnished by LawInsider is governed by their privacy policy.

LawInsider keeps track of the pages our customers visit within our websites in order to determine what Services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within the websites we operate to users whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. LawInsider uses tracking pixels to collect information that helps us provide our Service to you. Please note that any "do not track" signals sent by your web browser or other mechanism have no effect on the collection of personally identifiable information by LawInsider. In addition, other parties who perform data analytics for LawInsider, such as Google Analytics, may collect personally identifiable information about your online activities when you use our Services. Third party affiliates of LawInsider may have different policies with respect to "do not track" signals and LawInsider makes no representations with respect to such policies.

LawInsider uses tracking to create remarketing audiences of users based on user behavior/their visits to our website. LawInsider may also target these users with custom ads based on affinities/interests, geographic and demographic signals. LawInsider only shares browser-level data through third party vendor tracking such as Google Analytics. Users can opt out of these advertising features by visiting Google or resources like the NAI consumer opt-out page. LawInsider may use email addresses to target users with custom ads through 3rd party advertising platforms. LawInsider shares customer information with third parties to perform services (advertising) on our behalf.

LawInsider may disclose personal information when we are required to or we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order); to enforce or apply this Privacy Policy or our other policies or agreements; to initiate, render, bill, and collect for amounts owed to us; to protect our or our users' rights, property or safety; to protect our users from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of the Services; or if we believe that an emergency involving the danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires or justifies disclosure of personal information.

Information about our customers, including personal information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personal information could be transferred to third parties as one of LawInsider's business assets. In such an event, we will attempt to notify you before your personal information is transferred, but you may not have the right to opt out of any such transfer.

## 3\. Use of Cookies

Our website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you register an account with LawInsider, a cookie helps us recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to our website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Services.

## 4\. Security of your Personal Information

You are responsible for safeguarding and preventing unauthorized access to the user information and password that you use to access our Services. You agree not to disclose your password to any third party and you are responsible for any activity using your account, whether or not you authorized that activity. Please immediately notify LawInsider of any unauthorized use of your account.

LawInsider secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. In addition, LawInsider secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

## 5\. Children Under Thirteen

Our Services are not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and such use is prohibited by our Terms of Service. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you become aware that a child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

## 7\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

LawInsider may change the provisions of this Privacy Policy at any time, and will always post the most up-to-date version on our website.

## 8\. International Transfers

The Website is hosted in, and our Services are provided from, the United States. Accordingly, by providing your Personal Information through the Website, you consent to the transfer of your Personal Information from your country of residence to the United States. With regard to data transfers from the European Economic Area to the U.S., we have self-certified to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. For more information about our self-certification to the Privacy Shield Framework, please visit here.

## 9\. Contact Information

LawInsider welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. Please Contact Us.

For more information, please review our Terms of Service.
